Kyouma,
はっ！
フッフッフッ ハッハッハ…
フフフ ハッハハハ…
I want...
この俺が 救世主だと？
...you to be...
...the messiah.
くだらん！
俺は
狂気のマッドサイエンティスト
望みは 破壊と混沌だ！
フハッ ハッハハハ…
You want me to be the messiah?
ハッハハハ…
Ridiculous.
I am a mad scientist...
どうしちゃったんだぜ？
I desire chaos and destruction!
これより
過去を司る女神作戦を再開する
えっ？
下に まだ ブラウン氏いるけど？
What happened to him?
かまわん…
待って！
言ったはずよ 私は反対
We will now restart Operation Urd.
何を？
昼間は 協力的だったではないか
昼間って？
Mister Braun's still downstairs, man.
それじゃあ やっぱり…
I don't care!
Wait!
I told you.
ああ 実験は行われた
I'm against this.
Against it?
Ｄメールにより
既に 過去は変わっているのだ
This morning, you were helping me.
マジっすか？
This morning?
世界線が変わったっていうこと？
Then... I knew it.
恐らくな…
そのために お前たちは
Yes.
The experiment took place.
改変前の記憶を一部 失ったのだ
The D-mail has already changed the past.
それって 例のロト６が
どうとかってやつ？
Seriously?
The world line changed?
そうだ
で… どうして あんただけが
記憶を保っているのよ？
Yes, I think so.
Thus, you've lost some
of your memories from before the change.
タイターは言っていた
Is this about that Lotto-6 thing?
俺には 力があると
それを確かめるためにも
That's right.
もう一度 世界線を
移動させねばならないのだ
So why are you the only one who remembers?
力？
Titor told me that I have a power.
世界線を越えて なお
記憶を持ち続ける力
To prove it, we need to move world lines again.
魔眼 運命探知
A power?
The power to retain memories,
even across world line changes...
The magic eye: Reading Steiner.
Chaos Theory Homeostasis
はあ…
ふう…
ダル！
Daru?
送信履歴なし 着信は…
No record in the outbox...
おお～
Ｄメールは ５日前に届いてる
But as for the inbox,
the D-mail arrived five days ago.
成功ね…
過去 変わった？
It succeeded.
Did the past change?
なぜ そのことを覚えている？
Why do you remember that?
ああ…
５日前のダルに Ｄメールを送り
We sent a D-mail to Daru five days in the past,
フェイリス杯でのカードの配置を
知らせ
telling him the position of the cards,
ダルが優勝するはずが…
so he could win the Feyris Cup.
ああ まゆ氏？
Mayushii?
Question for you... In the Feyris Cup last week...
ちょっと 聞きたいんだけど
この前のフェイリス杯で 僕って…
えっ 負けた？ 瞬殺？
What? I lost? Immediately?
ああ… そう サンキュー じゃあ
I see... Thanks. Bye.
ああ…
ダルのメールでは
過去は変わらなかった
Daru's message didn't alter the past.
ゲームの流れは 変わったはずよ
With the way the game went,
it should have changed.
それくらいでは
世界線は 変動しないということだ
It wasn't enough to change world lines.
もっと
分かりやすく過去が変わったと
Then we need an easier way to tell
確認できるものでないと ダメか
if the past has changed.
ほう？
別に 実験賛成とか
そういうことじゃなくて…
I-It still isn't like I agree with
these experiments, okay?
で どう思ってるの？
So... What do you think?
あんただけ
記憶が継続してることについて
About you being the only one to remember?
言ったはずだ
魔眼 運命探知の力だと
I told you.
It's the power of the magic eye, Reading Steiner!
それを確かめるためにも
In order to see if that's true,
次は
お前に Ｄメールを送ってもらうぞ
I'll have you send the next D-mail.
私は いや
I don't want to.
タイムパラドックスが
気になるのか？
Worried about a time paradox?
過去を変えるなんて
It feels unfair to change the past.
なんか ひきょうな感じがするから
私の人生は たかだか18年だけど
改変なんか したくない
I've only lived eighteen years,
but I don't want to change any of them.
失敗したことも含めて
自分の人生なんだから…
They're all part of my life, even the failures.
だが 実験は大好き
But you love experiments, right?
そうだな？
す… 好きで悪いか！
I-Is that wrong?
すなわち
自分は 高みの見物を決め
In other words, you'll just sit back and watch,
他人を犠牲にして ほくそ笑む
as others sacrifice themselves.
うむ 実に
マッドサイエンティストだ
A true mad scientist.
もう いい！
Enough!
しかしだ 真面目な話… んっ？
But seriously...
From: Shining Finger
Subject: Please
I want to send
a D-mail, too.
真面目な話
Ｄメールを より完璧にするため…
But seriously...
If we're going to perfect the D-mail...
From: Shining Finger
Subject: Please?
It's okay, right?
Please!
Moeka
くっ…
やはり 実験を続けるしか…
...we'll have to continue our experiments...
桐生さん？
From: Shining Finger
Subject: I'm...
A lab member,
too, right?
Moeka
Kiryuu-san?
でえ～げ くどい！
Enough!
ダメ？
ああっ！
I can't?
あ～あ…
結局 押しきられてしまった
She overwhelmed us...
は～い おうちに着きました！
Okay, we're here!
クレープ おいしかったな～
うん！
Those crêpes were good...
Yeah.
ハッハ～
なんだ 暇そうじゃねえか
Hey! You look bored.
人を待ってるんですよ
I'm waiting for someone.
ううっ…
おら！
Hey, don't scare Nae!
綯を 怖がらせるんじゃねえって！
何もしてないでしょ？
I didn't do anything!
Come on, Nae.
さあ 綯 こんな野郎
相手にしないで さっさと行こうな
Let's leave this loser alone and go inside.
おはよう～！
Hi!
ああっ！ まゆりおねえちゃん！
Mayuri-oneechan!
トゥットゥル－！
フフッ…
これ あげる
I'll give this to you.
わあ ありがとう！
Thanks!
Here's one for Okarin, too!
はい オカリンにも
フフン
ふふっ… あっ？
ち～っす！
Yo!
鈴さん おはよう！
バイトのおねえちゃん！
Good morning, Suzu-san.
It's the part-timer girl!
ねえ ねえ…
あれから どうしたの？
Hey... What happened after that?
何がだ？
タイムマシンだよ！
With what?
The time machine!
ジョン･タイターに聞いたの？
Did you ask John Titor?
ああ… だが ヤツの言うことが
正しいのかどうか
Yeah, but I don't know if
what he says is accurate...
分からなくなってきた…
ええ～？
どのへんが？
ああ？
Which part?
なぜ そんなにムキになる？
Why are you so interested?
お前 さては タイターオタだな？
You're a Titor otaku, aren't you?
違うって…
あっ 紅莉栖ちゃん！
No.
Kurisu-chan!
トゥットゥルー！
グッド モーニング
Good morning.
おっ…
おお？
おっ？
おお～ また
火花を散らせていたわけですか
More sparks between you two?
何なのよ まったく
What's her problem, anyway?
ケンカは悲しいです
Fighting makes me sad.
あっ…
心配しないで 大丈夫だから
Don't worry! It's okay.
ありがとう
Thank you.
私的なメールは禁止だ
No private messages.
過去が変わったかどうか
確認しやすい
We want something simple, that will make it clear
シンプルな内容が望ましい
whether the past's changed.
｢４日前に
携帯の機種変更したけど
"I changed my cell phone four days ago,
変えない方がよかったって
自分に伝えたい｣
and I want to tell myself not to do it."
なるほど… 過去が変われば
桐生さんの携帯が変わる
I see.
So if the past changes,
you'll have a different cell phone.
一目瞭然ね
It would be obvious.
では 実験を開始する！
Then let us begin the experiment!
えいっ！
よ～し！
電話レンジ(仮) 始動！
Right! Activate the Phone Microwave
(name subject to change)!
うん？
真ん丸だ～
It's so round...
これは？
What is this?
凶真さんに頼まれたロト６
間違えてしまったので
I used the wrong number for
the Lotto-6 you asked me about.
その おわびです
This is my apology.
おお そ… そうか それは…
I... I see.
うむっ 良い心がけだ！
お前の心眼が開く日も
Good... Good to hear!
The day nears, when your heart's eye will open.
遠くはないだろう…
はい！
Yes!
じゃあ 僕は これで…
もう 行っちゃうの？
Excuse me, then.
You're leaving?
なんだか
お取り込み中みたいですし…
You seem busy.
失礼します
Goodbye.
今度は
まゆしぃのコス 着に来てよね
Wear Mayushii's cosplay sometime soon, okay?
ごっ ごめんなさい
僕 そういうのは ちょっと…
I-I'm sorry.
I'm not really into that...
やっぱり ダメ？
似合うと思うんだけどな
So you won't?
I think you'd look great...
じゃっ また
Goodbye.
うん バイバ～イ
Bye-bye!
いい子ね
うん
Good kid, huh?
Yeah.
ああっ！
おおっ！ くっ くう…
This feeling again.
また この感覚
ということは…
Which means...
The past changed?
過去が 変わった？
なっ ああ…
シャッ…
閃光の指圧師は どこへ行った？
Wh-Where's Shining Finger?
シャイ…は？
Shi...
日本語で おｋ
Japanese... Do you speak it?
はっ… はあ！
はっ！
ルカ子は 来なかったのか？
Rukako didn't stop by?
るか君？ うん 来てないけど
Rukako? Nope.
では 萌郁は？ 萌郁は どうした？
Then, Moeka... Where's Moeka?
萌郁さん… 誰？
Moeka-san? Who's that?
はっ… 桐生萌郁だ！
今日は 来ていないのか？
Kiryuu Moeka!
She wasn't here today?
どうなんだ！
ええ？
Well?
Who's that?
それ 誰？
えっ…
桐生萌郁？
私も 聞いたことがない
Kiryuu Moeka... I've never heard that name.
なんだと!?
What?
はっ まさか… また Ｄメールを？
Another D-mail?
えっ？
ちょっ それ どういうこと？
Wh-What do you mean?
過去が変わり
The past changed,
and Moeka's very existence disappeared?
萌郁という人間の存在そのものが
消えた…
Impossible!
まさか！
着信履歴には７月31日まで
萌郁のメールが残っている
Up to July 31st, my inbox still has messages from her.
あっ…
"Something wrong?"
"Sorry, I'm kind of busy."
"I'll message you later."
つまり ４日前
In other words,
メールを受け取ってからの
桐生萌郁さん？
the past altered in such a way that,
ever since four days ago,
彼女の行動が変わり
ラボには来なかった
when she received that message,
this Kiryuu... Moeka-san
というふうに 過去が改変された
changed her actions and never came to the lab.
そういうことだな…
I suppose so.
それに
今回も あんただけが覚えている
And this time, only you remember it.
The Reading Steiner, was it?
その… 運命探知だっけ？
ちなみに この造語 恥ずかし…
By the way, just saying that embarrasses me.
I don't think you should call it that.
やめた方がいいと思う
I'm not interested in your personal opinion.
お前の個人的な見解は 必要ない
はあ…
世界線を越えて 記憶を継続する力
The power to maintain memories across world lines.
ホントに 本物なの？
Is it real?
お待たせ～
Here I am!
We'll talk tomorrow.
話は また明日
オカリン また明日
See you tomorrow, Okarin!
この力は本物だ
I really do have that ability.
I want you to be the messiah.
でも
That means...
俺は…
I...
まったく あいつら よく
ラボで 寝泊まりできるわよね
I'm amazed they can sleep at the lab...
それが マッドサイエンティスト
なんだって
He said it's 'cause he's a mad scientist.
あっ そうだ 今度
みんなで お泊まり会しようよ！
I know! Let's all sleep over at the lab!
男ども抜きならね
If the guys aren't there.
あっ そうだ
私のホテルに来ない？
I know, why not come to my hotel?
いいの？
もちろん
Could I?
Of course.
Sure!
うん
じゃあ 今度 おじゃまするね！
Okay, I'll come over soon!
うん？
Ruka-kun?
るか君 トゥットゥルー！
Yeah...
うん うん… ええ～!? ホント？
Yeah... What?!
Really?
なに～!?
What?!
You didn't bring the Magic Blade Samidare?
妖刀五月雨を
持ってこなかっただと？
Um...
ダメだよ オカリン
Don't say that, Okarin!
Today, Ruka-kun is my guest.
るか君は 今日は
まゆしぃのお客さんなんだよ
まゆしぃのコスを
着てくれるんだね！
He's going to wear my cosplay!
あっ… ぼっ 僕…
Um... I...
Come on. Let's transform, Ruka-kun. Transform!
さあ さあ るか君 変身しよう
変身 変身～！
わっ だっ だから 僕…
Um, I mean, I...
ほら 服を脱ぎ脱ぎして～
Let's take off your clothes...
ああ そんな所 触らないで！
あっ… 分かった
No, don't touch me there!
Okay!
僕 一人で着るから
だから あっちに…
I'll put it on myself!
So leave me alone.
ううん これ着るのに
コツが要るからね
You have to know the trick to putting this on.
P-Please... Don't take off my clothes!
お願いだから 脱がさないで…
すごく… 百合です
This is very yuri.
違うな ルカ子は男だ
No. Rukako is a guy.
ということは…
Which means...
さらに けしからん！
It's even better!
ヘヘッ
まっ…
It's Kirari-chan from Rai-Net.
雷ネットのキラリちゃんだよ
あっ ああ…
思ったとおり
かわいいよ るか君！
You're as cute as I imagined, Ruka-kun!
This is really embarrassing...
こんな格好… 恥ずかしい
大丈夫 かわいいは正義だから！
It's okay!
Cute is justice.
I want to get a low-angle shot of this.
これは
ローアングラー化したくなる
What do you think, Okarin?
オカリンは どう思う？
そうだなあ…
That's right...
ああっ…
俺だ 今 強烈な精神攻撃を受けた
It's me!
I've just been victimized by a
fierce psychological attack!
くっ マズい！
心が 心が侵食されてく…
This is bad!
My soul... My soul is being devoured!
どっ どうしたんですか？
凶真さん
Wh-What's wrong, Kyouma-san?
What's with him?
また 何を騒いでるんだか
紅莉栖ちゃん トゥットゥルー！
Kurisu-chan!
うん？
はっ！
HENTAI助手よ！ 全身を
ねめ回すように見つめるのは よせ
Stop staring, pervert assistant.
してないわよ！
I'm not staring!
Further win!
また けしからん展開！
What do you think of this cosplay?
どう？
このコス るか君に似合ってる？
Does it look good?
へっ？
ええ… とっても キュートね
Yes... It's very cute.
C-Cute... Well, I...
キュ キュートだなんて そんな…
Let's try on the others!
ほかの衣装も着てみよう！
あ～あ 待って！
今日 ここに来たのは
Wait!
I came here because I had a request for you.
凶真さんたちに
お願いがあったからなんです
You didn't come here to wear my cosplay?
コスを着に来てくれたんじゃ
なかったの？
ち 違うって 言ってるのに…
話を聞いてくれないんだもん
I-I said no. But you wouldn't listen to me...
I'm sorry. I was just really happy.
ああ ごめんね
うれしくって つい…
で… 頼みというのは？
So what did you want to ask?
Actually...
あの 実は…
うん？
僕も 過去に
メールを送らせてほしいんです！
I want you to let me send a message to the past!
えっ？
昨日…
I came by...
ロト６を外してしまった
おわびをしようと思って
...to apologize for having missed
the Lotto-6 yesterday. And then...
そしたら…
まさか またＤメールを？
Another D-mail?
えっ？
ちょっ それ どういうこと？
Wh-What do you mean?
The past changed,
and Moeka's very existence disappeared?
過去が変わり
萌郁という人間の存在そのものが
消えた… まさか！
Impossible!
すみませんでした！
I'm sorry for listening when I shouldn't have!
盗み聞きするつもりなんて
なかったんですけど…
I didn't mean to!
るか君 過去に
どんなメールを送りたいの？
Ruka-kun, what kind of message
do you want to send to the past?
実は 僕…
Actually, I...
I want to be a girl!
女の子になりたいんです！
はっ？
ああ…
I don't like the way I look.
僕 自分の容姿が
あんまり好きじゃなくて
女の子になれれば
少しは自信が出るかなって
I think I'd feel better about myself
if I could be a girl...
I've always felt that way.
昔から そう思ってたんです
ちょ… ちょっと待って
W-Wait a second...
いったい
彼女は 何を言っているの？
What is she saying?
フフン 助手よ
Assistant, you appear to have
made a fatal mistake.
どうやら
お前は 決定的な間違いを
犯しているようだ
間違い？
Mistake?
ルカ子は女ではない… 男だ
Rukako is no girl.
He's a guy.
What kind of joke is that?
何の冗談だ それは…
浅はかだなあ お前も科学者なら
You don't believe me...
If you call yourself a scientist,
then see for yourself.
自分の目で
しっかり 確かめてみろ
こんな かわいい子が
男の子のはず…
Such a cute girl couldn't be a guy.
ごめん ちょっと…
Excuse me for a second.
はっ！
Are you okay?
大丈夫？
僕 本気なんです
I'm serious!
本気で 女の子になりたいんです！
I really want to be a girl!
Please!
お願いします
But I don't know if sending a D-mail
しかし Ｄメールを送ったところで
性別を変えることなど
would be enough to change your gender.
できるかどうか…
聞いたことがあるんです
I heard of something...
赤ちゃんが おなかにいる間に
お肉をいっぱい食べると 男の子が
That if you eat lots of meat
when a baby is in your tummy,
you'll have a boy.
With a lot of vegetables, you'll have a girl.
野菜をいっぱい食べると
女の子が産まれるって
お母さんに
｢野菜を いっぱい食べてね｣って
You want us to send a D-mail, telling your mom
Ｄメールを送るってこと？
to eat lots of vegetables?
Would that be possible?
はい ダメでしょうか？
Very well.
よかろう
お前の望みを かなえてやろう
I shall grant your wish.
はっ…
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
よかったね るか君！
はい！
Good for you, Ruka-kun!
Yes!
性別を変えるなんて
さすがに マズいんじゃね？
Isn't changing someone's gender a bad idea?
野菜を食ったぐらいで
そんなことが あり得ると思うか？
Do you think it's possible to affect it,
just by eating vegetables?
そうね…
科学的な根拠がある話でもないし
That's true.
There's no scientific evidence for it.
He must have really been worried about it
悩んだ上でのことだろう
if that makes him feel better.
それで気が済むのなら
Rukako, from now on, you're Lab Member 006!
ルカ子！ 今日から お前は
我がラボの一員 ラボメンNo.006だ
はっ はい！
さて 早速 実験を…
Y-Yes.
Let us begin the experiment...
お前 今年 17歳だったな
Wait, you're seventeen this year, right?
えっ… あっ はい
Huh? Yes.
In other words, you were born in 1993...
つまり 1993年生まれ…
What of it?
それが どうかしたの？
When did cell phones become popular in Japan?
携帯電話が 日本に
普及し始めたのは いつごろだ？
あっ…
1996年ごろっぽい
It looks like it was around 1996.
メールの機能が付くのは
さらに 遅いかも…
And they may only later have
gotten messaging capability.
In other words, when Urushibara-san was born,
つまり
漆原さんが生まれた時点では
there's a good chance his mom
didn't own a cell phone.
お母さんが 携帯電話を
持っていない可能性がある
Then we can't send the D-mail?
じゃあ Ｄメール送れないの？
Oh, no.
そんな…
We could change it, so it sends sinister microwaves.
毒電波を飛ばせるように
改造するとか？
毒電波は
あんたたちだけで 十分…
You have enough sinister microwaves for everyone.
Good... Insult me more.
ああ いいよ～
もっと 罵ってくれて おｋだよ～
That's fine...
I see.
そうかあ フ～ッフフフ…
あ～ 自分の才能が恐ろしい
I'm terrified by my own talent!
また 何を言い出すんだか…
Not this again...
If she doesn't have a cell phone,
send it to her pager!
携帯がないのなら
ポケベルに送れば いいじゃない！
Pagers...
｢ポケベル 電波によって
小型受信機に合図を送るシステム
A system using EM waves to
transmit messages to small receivers.
During the 1990s,
they enjoyed enormous popularity.
1990年代に爆発的に普及
携帯電話の普及により
下火となる｣
The emergence of cellular phones
rendered them obsolete.
Pagers?
ポケベル？
これが… 初めて見ました！
I've never seen one!
詳しいな…
セレセブならぬ セレサーか？
You're very knowledgeable.
I guess you were a Cel-Pager, not a Cel-7?
そこに書いてある 自分で読め
It's written right there.
Why not read it yourself?
うん？
ラボメンNo.006 漆原るか
Lab Member 006, Urushibara Ruka!
ファーストミッションだ
It's time for your first mission.
Find out if your mother had a pager.
母親が ポケベルを持っていたか
調べ その番号を入手せよ！
And get that number!
Y-Yes, sir!
はっ はい！
お母さん ポケベル持ってました！
これが 番号です
My mom had a pager!
Here's the number.
でかしたぞ！ メールの文面は
You did it!
You thought of what to write, right?
考えてきたのだろうな？
はい！
Yes!
"Eat vegetables for a healthy child."
I heard you can only send eighteen hiragana...
平仮名で18文字しか送れないと
聞いたので…
You can only send numbers to a pager.
ポケベルは
数字しか 送れないのよね
Transform these to numbers...
これを 数字に変換して…
One sec.
ちょい待ち… 濁点は 数字２個で
You need two digits for voiced consonants.
表現しないとダメっぽい
えっ？
What?
You can send a total of thirty-six English letters.
送れるのは 半角で36文字まで
その文章だと ４文字オーバー
That message puts you four characters over.
Then...
ふむ では…
これを 数字に変換すると？
How about we turn this into numbers?
Eat veggies for a healthy child.
Okay, starting it up.
いいか 起動するぞ！
はい！
All right.
Is this really okay?
本当に 大丈夫かな？
Don't worry about it.
心配するな
はあっ！ うっ…
うわっ うう…
はっ！
My Reading Steiner activated!
運命探知が 発動した
Which means...
ということは…
I see... Some people are like that, huh?
なるほど～ こういう人もいるのね
Yes, it's cute!
うん これは かわいいです
Ruka-chan, I think you'd look great
in something like this.
るかちゃんには
こういうの 絶対 似合うと思うな
そっ そうかな？
Y-You think?
うん？
This is...
これは…
You pervert!
こら HENTAI！
どこを見つめている？
Where are you staring?
No, I mean...
いやっ そうではなく…
待てよ？
Wait.
It's difficult to ask if Rukako became a girl.
ルカ子は 女になれたか？
とは 聞きづらい
But...
しかし…
This failed.
これは 失敗だな…
What kind of perverted thing are you imagining?
だ～か～ら ニヤニヤと
いったい どんな HENTAI的行為を
想像している？
Jeez, Okarin!
もう～ オカリン！
まったく…
I can't take my eyes off
you two perverts for a minute.
あんたたち HENTAIコンビは
油断も隙もないんだから…
I'm not a pervert! I'm a perverted gentlemen!
HENTAIじゃないよ
HENTAI紳士だよ！
It doesn't matter... It really doesn't matter!
どうでもいい！
ホント どうでもいい
But...
だが… 確かに 世界線は移動した
The world line changed.
何かが変わったのだ
Something happened...
But what?
いったい… 何が？